Lydon Campbell

Music producer, composer, and engineer with eight years of experience. Proficient in Protools, Ableton Live, Reason, Logic, and FL Studio. Experienced in managing live recording spaces as well as in making detailed edits to audio waveforms.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BMG, Intern - Mechanical Licensing

FEB 2023 - MAY 2023 — Nashville, TN

- Tracked down missing writers using social media to acquire publisher and split information and move them out of copyright control
- Created and submitted licensing requests to CMRRA
- Cleared over 250 products out of the company's backlog on CMRRA Direct
- Created a system to log and address discrepancies between our records and publishing and split information contained within the licenses issued by CMRRA

New Summit Academy, Music Production Teaching Assistant

NOV 2018 - NOV 2019 — Atenas, Costa Rica

- Drove an independent effort to reimagine the recording studio on campus, adding a digital composition workstation and directing the purchase of updated equipment
- Managed the day to day use of other students which entailed keeping a schedule, caring for the equipment, and ensuring the live room and control room remained clean and organized at all times
- Introduced fellow students to digital music production and taught them the basic skills needed to independently explore the subject further

KJMedia Productions, Composer

AUG 2021 - FEB 2023 — Los Angeles, CA - Milan, Italy - Bali, Indonesia

 Composed and produced instrumental backing tracks for all videos put out by the company

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Los Angeles Film School — Associates, Music Production

Spring 2020 - Spring 2021

Dexter Southfield/New Summit Academy — *High School*

SEP 2015 - NOV 2019

- GPA 3.41
- SAT 1400
- ACT 33

Nashville, TN 37205 (781) 401-0415 lydoncampbell77@gmail.com

SKILLS

Proficient in Protools, Ableton Live, Reason, Logic, and FL Studio

Experienced in recording live bands and solo acts

Comfortable making detailed edits to raw audio waveforms